

Nicolás Gonzalez Full Stack Developer

Contact me

- +598 98 160 944
- gonzalezvidal.nicolas@gmail.com
- Montevideo, Uruguay
 - Nicolás González Vidal linkedin.com/in/nicolás-gonzález-vidal
- nicogz90 https://github.com/nicogz90

Skills



CSS 3

JavaScript



Node.js nede

MongoDB



Languages

advanced English - First Certificate (FCE) Cambridge University Montevideo, Uruguay / Dic 2005

Spanish - native



About me

Hi! I'm Nicolás and i'm very excited about starting my work experience in the IT field. I'm a Civil Engineer, specialized in BIM design with +9 years of experience as a site manager in multi-disciplinary projects.

A year ago I began to focus my knowledge and training towards programming, taking a Full Stack web development course, which sparked my curiosity and passion in the

Currently, I continue incorporating knowledge and putting my acquired skills into practice, while looking for an entry-level opportunity where I can develop, grow and contribute the best of myself.



Education

Hack Academy

Montevideo, Uruguay Mar 2022 - Oct 2022

PC Carrier Barcelona, Spain

UDELAR

Montevideo, Uruguay Mar 2008 - Mar 2016

Full Stack developer

Front-End > HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap Vue. React & React Native Back-End > Node.js, Express, MySQL, MongoDB

3D BIM design specialist

Revit Architecture, Structure and Installations. CYPE, concrete and steel structures design.

Structural Civil Engineer



Experience

Freelance

3D Proyects 2019 - Actual 3D proyects design and modeling

Saceem

Site manager Oct 2017 - Actual

ATSH Steel

Oct 2016 - Oct 2017

Site manager

Construction site management

- Civil works for extra high voltage substation
- UPM Port: Assembly of 7,000 tons of steel structure, 70,000 m2 roof steel sheet and installation of 1,000 m of rails for overhead cranes.
- Assembly of steel structure, panels and precast concrete at logistics hub project
- Supply control and site coordination for divers steel structure projects.

Medina v Possamai

Site manager Jun 2016 – Sep 2016 - Management of sanitation, pipe laying and sewerage works

Saceem

Technical assistant Abr 2015 - May 2016

- Site management support
- Surveys and calculations

IMM

Technical assistant Sep 2013 - Abr 2015 - Road maintenance survey